괜찮아, 패드 3개 있어 많을수록 재밌으니까
No problem. I have three controllers. The more the merrier.
데이트야 오늘 데이트 여기서 하기로 했어
It's a date. I have a date coming over.
그런 결론을 내지 못했다고 내 탓 하면 안 돼
You can't blame me for not jumping to that conclusion.
왜? 내가 데이트 하는 게 뭐가 그리 이상해?
Why? What's so unusual about me having a date?
통계적으로.. - 알았어
Statistically speaking... - All right, all right.
그건 그렇지만 오늘 데이트가 있긴 하니까
Nevertheless, I have one now and I'd appreciate it if you would,
오늘은 자리를 비켜주면 정말 좋겠어
make yourself scarce.
난 2개의 박사 학위를 가진 이론 물리학자이면서
I'm a published theoretical physicist with two doctorates
일반적인 시험으로는 측정 불가능한 IQ를 가졌다고
얼마나 내가 모자라겠어? (scarce - 모자라다는 뜻이 있음)
How much scarcer could I be?